{
  "Ethereum Basics": [
    {
      "question": "The founder of Ethereum was",
      "ans": "Vitalik Buterin"
    },
    {
      "question": "The highlight feature of Ethereum was",
      "ans": "Smart Contracts"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the native token of Ethereum called?",
      "ans": "Ether"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the main network of Ethereum called?",
      "ans": "Mainnet"
    }
  ],

  "Cryptography": [
    {
      "question": "What type of consensus mechanism did Ethereum use before Ethereum 2.0?",
      "ans": "Proof of Work"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Ethereum's Cryptographic Hash Function?",
      "ans": "Keccak-256"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which hashing algorithm is used on Public keys to get the Ethereum address?",
      "ans": "Keccak-256"
    }
  ],

  "Transactions": [
    {
      "question": "Does Ethereum Transaction include a Nonce?",
      "ans": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the fuel of Ethereum?",
      "ans": "Gas"
    },
    {
      "question": "Gas is calculated in which unit?",
      "ans": "Wei"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which protocol does the Ethereum network use for transaction propagation?",
      "ans": "Flood Routing"
    }
  ],
  "Smart Contracts": [
    {
      "question": "Smart contracts are programmed using which language",
      "ans": "Solidity"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the first line of a solidity program include?",
      "ans": "License Identifier"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does solidity have a predefined data type for addresses?",
      "ans": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which concept in solidity is similar to Classes in other programming languages?",
      "ans": "Contract"
    }
  ]
}